史前巨鳄
替海獭贴标签真的有钱赚吗
They actually pay you for this, to tag beaver?
你猜
Imagine.
你在讽刺我吗
Was that, like, sarcastic?
你们渔猎局都瞧不起乡下警长
'Cause I know what you Fish and Game guys think of county sheriffs.
老爱说些刺耳的话
We know you like to give these one-word, sarcastic answers.
是啊
Gee.
你问我
You ask me,
动物干什么是它们的事
what an animal does in the wild is his own business.
只要不要影响人类就行
So long as he doesn't do it to man.
我想这句话是马克吐温说的
I think Mark Twain said that.
我想不是吧
Yeah, I think he didn't.
不过既然是你说的就算是吧
But since you said it, I guess we're covered.
这些人说话都带刺
Everyone's a comedian, sarcastic.
# I'm sleepin'
# And right in the middle of a good dream #
# And all at once I wake up #
# From something that keeps knocking at my brain #
# Before I go insane #
# I hold my pillow to my head... #
Aah! Aah!
# So what am I so afraid of?. #
# I'm afraid that I'm not sure of... #
救命
Help!
# I think I love you #
# Isn't that what life is made of?. #
啊
Aah ha!
别松手
Ohh! Don't let go!
噢 不
Oh ho ho!
啊
Aah!
我的天呀
Aw, Jesus Christ.
凯莉
Kelly?
柯文
Hey, Kevin.
嗨
Hi.
我能跟你谈谈吗
Listen, uh, could I steal you for a minute?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我在静坐
Heavy breathing, meditating.
静坐?
Meditating?
对 为了减轻压力
Yes. To relieve stress.
你教我要靠呼吸放松
Remember, Myra, you're the one who taught me all about breathing.
干嘛呀? 你在生小孩吗
Yes, but you're doing Lamaze. are you giving birth?
深呼吸才能放松心情
If you're upset, long, deep breaths.
我被柯文甩掉
Kevin dumped me.
我知道了
I know.
他跟你说的?
He told you?
我有第一手消息
Well, I sort of had, uh, inside information.
你?
You?
那是在你之前
It started before you, Kelly.
我绝对不会...
I never would have--
你?
You?
那只是一夜情 而且我们觉得这事就这么过去了
It was just a quick thing that we thought was over,
结果却没有
and...it's not over.
你跟柯文
You and Kevin.
我该怎么说
I--l wish I could say something to...
人都要随心所欲
the heart wants what the heart wants.
"缅因州渔猎局长"
基奥警长
Sheriff Keough?
是
Yeah.
我是渔猎局的杰克·威尔斯
Fish and Game. Jack Wells.
最近会有熊出来伤人吗
Any recent bear attacks?
没有
This was no bear.
熊不会在水底吃人
Bears don't attack people underwater.
也许是一只食人海獭
Probably a beaver, then.
你真是尖酸刻薄
Ah, a whole sentence sarcastic.
他被咬成一半?
That the way he came out of the water?
嗯
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
柯文 近来如何? 怎么样
Hey, Kevin, what's going on? What's happening?
你的家人好吗?
How's it goin'? How's your family? Good?
棒呆了 幸会
It's great. So nice to see you.
快给我滚
Fuck off.
这是公事
This is business.
缅因州出了意外
There was an accident in Maine.
有人在湖底被咬死
Some guy got killed by something in a lake.
大概是只熊 他们找到一颗牙齿
Probably a bear, but they found a tooth.
牙齿?
A tooth?
只是碎片
A fragment of a tooth,
很大一只熊的牙齿
one they say couldn't have come from any bear.
很古老自远古的恐龙
Evidently it looks prehistoric, like maybe a dinosaur.
原来是这样 他可能是被恐龙咬死的
Oh, well, then I'm sure that that's what it was. He was killed by a dinosaur.
还有其他事吗
Is there anything else?
我派你去调查
I, uh, want you to go there.
什么?
What?
也许是空穴来风 不过这是古生物学家的工作
It's probably nothing, but you're a paleontologist. This is what we do.
你这是什么意思
What do you mean, this is what we do?
我要你查明真相
I'd like you to check out this tooth.
我不是田野调查员
I'm not a field person.
这次我希望你去
Well, on this one, I would like you to be.
你要我去缅因州看一颗牙
You want me to go to Maine to look at a tooth?
这是蜜拉的点子 对吧?
Oh, this was Myra's idea, wasn't it?
当然
Oh, of course.
让我离开一阵子冷静一下
Get me out of the office for a few days, wait till I cool off...
不是这样的
it has nothing to do with that.
我不做调查 也不去缅因州
I don't do field work, and even if I did, Maine?
我对树木会过敏
I'm allergic to timber.
- 凯莉 - 我不去缅因州
- Kelly. - I am not going to Maine.
我死也不去
I'm not going to Maine.
想都别想
It's ridiculous.
飞越山头会有点颠簸
It's gonna be rough as we go over these mountains.
没关系 谢谢你
Yeah, that's fine. Thank you.
我只想说一声
We're doing the best we can.
别跟我说话
Could you not talk to me?
谢谢你
Thank you.
他狂叫着就扑上来
Just came up screaming.
他说了些什么
What did he say?
他只咽了一口气就挂了
Just kind of gurgled. He was pretty much dead.
你什么都没看到
You didn't see anything?
之前湖面很平静
The lake was calm until up he came.
牙齿在里面
The tooth is in here.
这里是停尸间
Oh, that's-- that's the morgue.
是的
Yes.
里面有尸体吗
Well, is the dead guy in there?
所以这里才叫做停尸间
That's where they keep them.
你要我把牙齿拿出来吗
Look...you want me to bring the tooth out here?
不用
No.
不
No. Let's...
你先请
After you.
这是爬虫类 并不是化石
This is reptilian. And this is not a fossil.
你真的是从他身上拔下来的
You really pulled this out of this guy?
没错
Yes, I did.
我要用显微镜观察
I'll need to get a microscopic look at it.
尽管用
There you go.
太好了
Great.
也许我应该看看
Maybe I should see--
最好不要
I wouldn't.
我又不是没看过死人
I can deal with dead men--bodies.
攻击持续多久?
How long did this attack go on for?
几秒钟 八秒 最多十秒钟
Seconds. 8 maybe 10.
他上来就是这样
Oh, and, uh, this is how he came up to the boat?
是的
Yes.
我想去看那座湖
I'd like to see this lake.
方圆25里都没人住
Nobody lives within 25 miles of it,
除了住湖畔的一对老夫妇
except some old couple who live right on the lake.
学生偶尔会跑来裸泳
Teenagers trek in every once in a while to skinny-dip.
没有人失踪过
None have disappeared.
也没发生不寻常的事
None have spotted anything unusual.
问过那对老夫妇了吗
Did you talk to the old couple?
还没有
Not yet.
我们还有什么支援
What kind of backup do we have?
我们?
We?
怎么了
What?
什么鬼博物馆会派人来这儿
I'm a little unclear as to why the museum would send somebody here.
你对博物馆有意见?
You gotta thing against museums?
我没有意见
No, I got nothing against museums.
你有去过吗?
Ever been in one?
那是什么
What is that?
轻型气压式火炮枪
Lightweight forward-area air-device unit.
只要一枪就能轰掉这怪物
Whatever's out there, one shot with this, it's dead.
你带这玩意干嘛
Why exactly would you have that?
天啊
God.
有蚊子 我最恨蚊于
Mosquitoes. I gotta thing about mosquitoes.
准备好了就走吧
If you're all set, let's go.
救星来了
We're saved.
纽约博物馆派人来支援我们
A museum in New York just sent us some additional backup.
我是凯莉·斯科特
Kelly Scott.
杰克·威尔斯
Jack Wells.
嗨
Hi.
是什么鬼博物馆派你来的吗
Uh, some museum sent you, huh?
你们都对博物馆不爽吗
What, are we all museum bigots in Maine?
她讲话很冲
She's rude sarcastic.
你们俩很速配
You two should get along.
女士 你不能跟来
I'm afraid I can't let you go with us, ma'am.
基奥警长说可以
Sheriff Keough said I could.
渔猎局的权力比警长大
Unfortunately, Fish and Game supersedes the sheriff.
这是什么道理?
Why do you have to supersede? Maybe I might be of--
女士 这可不是探险之旅
Ma'am, look, this isn't some kind of fact-finding expedition.
我知道
Yes, I know that.
也不是远足
It's not a science trip.
别这么傲慢 好吗
Could you be a little more condescending?
我不是三岁小孩
'Cause I'm not real great with subtlety.
湖中有个怪物咬死人
Something in that lake killed somebody, right?
我很感激你想帮忙
I appreciate you're trying to help.
谢谢你带一瓶杀虫剂来
I'm really glad that you brought the raid.
这样好多了
Now, that's better.
女士 没用的
Ma'am, it's not gonna work--
你再叫我女士我就告你 在今日的法律规定是可行的
If you call me "ma'am" one more time, I'll sue you, and with today's laws, it's possible.
她很高竿
She's good.
我不会干扰你们
Look, I won't interfere.
要不然就叫警长逮捕我
And if I do, you've got a sheriff handy to arrest me,
也许你会觉得我让你没面子
but I understand if I threaten your Fish and Game authority--
对不起
Excuse me.
你们要去抓湖中怪物吗
Is it true you're going to look for some kind of monster in Black Lake?
那是个意外
Well, we're just gonna investigate an accident.
没有怪物
There's no monster.
个人被咬成两半
We heard a man was bit in half.
那只是意外
Well, there was an accident.
仅此而已 不用担心
That's all. It's nothing to worry about.
拜托
Oh, please.
走吧
All right. Let's go.
我先生两年前就过世了
Well, my husband passed away. It's been almost 2 years now.
警局并没有记录
My department doesn't have any record of that,
毕太太
Mrs. Bickerman.
很抱歉 我只是不喜欢记录
Well, I'm sorry. Incomplete records haunt me so.
你先生的死因是什么?
What was the cause of your husband's death,ma'am, do you know?
我们不想多管闲事 不过他是不是因为生病
We don't mean to invade your privacy, but was he ill? Was he sick?
还是被吞掉?
Was he swallowed?
警长
Sheriff!
我们来此的原因是
Uh, Mrs. Bickerman, the reason we're here.
昨天有人被湖底的动物吃掉
A man was fatally attacked yesterday by some animal in this lake.
你知道你先生是怎么死的吗
Do you know how your husband died?
知道
Oh, yes.
我把他杀死了
I killed him.
你杀了他?
You killed him?
是的
Oh, yes.
你是怎么杀死他的?
and how would you have accomplished this, ma'am?
呃
Well...
他病得很重却不肯看医生
He was very sick,and--and he refused to go to a doctor.
有时候清醒有时候糊涂
He'd be coherent one day and incoherent the next.
他清醒时叫我结束他的痛苦
And, well, one coherent day he asked me to end his suffering.
他一直不断地求我
And, um...he kept insisting and insisting
最后我只好答应
and then, well, finally I just gave in,
我用煎锅K他 再把他埋起来
and I hit him on the head with a skillet,then buried him out at the bulkhead.
不信的话可以挖出来看
Well, dig him up if you don't believe me,
福尔摩斯
Sherlock.
半哩外有块空地
Half mile up there's a clearing.
湖水怎么了? 好黑哦
What's with the water? It's so black.
一点波浪都没有
There's no waves or anything.
本来要取名为宁静湖
Well, they wanted to call it "Lake Placid,"
有人说这名字被取过了
but somebody said that name was taken.
真可惜
It's too bad.
到了那儿帐蓬就应该搭好了
Tents were sent ahead. They should already be set up by the time we get there.
帐蓬?
Tents?
我们要睡帐蓬?
We're staying in tents?
我说这两天是要露营
I told you, 2 days we'd have to camp.
我以为你是说度假木屋
Yes, camp, but I thought that meant "Ramada lnn."
你可没提到帐蓬 有马桶吗?
I never heard tents. Will there be toilets?
也许该把你送回去
Maybe we should just take you back.
就因为我习惯坐马桶?
Why, because I prefer a toilet?
精糕
Oh, God.
我忘了带卫生纸
We forgot to pack feminine napkins.
现在你跟他同一国 是吗
Oh, so you're with him now? Are you taking his side?
我没这么说
I didn't say a word.
我干脆把毒藤当卫生纸擦
Oh, no, maybe I should just wipe myself with some leafy little piece of poison oak.
然后像个猴子猛抓屁股这样
And then I could spend the whole day scratching my ass, blending in with the natives.
你就肯跟我同国
Then you'd be back on my side.
你不说我们也知道你是纽约客
You know, you really don't have to bother telling people you're from New York.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
什么?
What?
我看到什么
There. I thought I saw something.
好像是根树枝
Looks like a branch.
我的天
Oh, my God.
嘿
Hey.
你是故意丢我的
You threw it at me!
我只是不小心放手了而已
I just let go of it.
你是故意丢我的
You threw it at me!
你看到吗
Did you see that? Oh!
女士
Ma'am!
别再打我
Stop hitting me.
别向我乱丢东西
Don't throw heads at me!
别叫我女士
Stop calling me "ma'am!"
老天爷
Aw, Jesus.
天啊
Oh, God.
警长
So, sheriff...
你手下有几名警员?
how many deputies you got?
怎样?
What?
那会是熊吗?
Could it be a bear?
这儿的熊很大
I mean, the bears get big here, right?
大熊不可能一口咬掉麋鹿的头
Hmm. I don't think a bear could bite off a moose's head.
你的东西都在这儿
Everything you need should be in there.
很好
Ok. Good. Good.
你要一起睡吗?
So will we be tent-mates then?
不 这是你的
Nope. This is all yours.
真是太好了
Ohh. Great.
太好了
Excellent.
要什么尽管说
If there's anything else you need...
我想问你一件事
Uh, one thing I wanted to ask you.
一个女孩子在野外安全吗
Uh, what's it like to be a woman in the woods of Maine?
这些臭男人不会野性大发吧
I mean, the guys don't turn all horny or anything like they did in Deliverance, right?
我就知道你在那里
I knew you were there.
你从未来过这儿 对吧
Never been to Maine before, huh?
我很讲究卫生 不太受欢迎
I have good hygiene. I'm not welcome.
你为什么要来
Why are you here, really?
我说过了
I told you.
博物馆不会派人到荒郊野外
A museum doesn't send an investigator into the woods--
你凭什么这么说
How would you know what a museum would or would not do exactly?
他们更不会派讨厌帐篷的人来
Well, even if they did,I doubt whether he or she would have problems with tents.
我是住不惯帐篷
So I don't like tents. Why--
你住不惯帐篷 受不了蚊子
Oh, you don't like tents, and you don't like mosquitoes.
谁受得了蚊子呀
Well, nobody likes mosquit--
看你的指甲
Look at your fingernails.
我的指甲怎么了?
What's wrong with my fingernails?
打死你也不会跑到野外
You have as much business being in the woods as Emily Post.
没道理
No, it doesn't make sense.
大老远要你来看牙齿
They sent you out here to examine a tooth.
现在跑到湖这儿来干嘛?
And what are you doing out here on the lake?
糟了
Oh, no.
怎么了?
What?
不会是他吧
If this is who I think it is...
是他
It is.
谁?
Who?
赫克托·西尔
Hector Cyr.
有钱的神话学教授
He's this rich, kook mythology professor.
你认识他吗?
You know him?
他跟博物馆合作过
He's done some work with our museum.
他也在世界各地
He also treks the world to s...
干嘛?
What?
跟鳄鱼游泳
To swim with crocodiles.
鳄鱼
Crocodiles?
他一定认为这儿有鳄鱼
If he's here, he must think you've got one.
我不是科学天才 但我知道缅因州不可能有鳄鱼
I admit I'm no brain scientist,but I do know there's no way a crocodile could be in Maine, right?
你比我先到
You beat me!
讨厌
Balls!
好棒的一座湖
Splendid lake, eh?
我在湖上才能大展雄风
Became a man on a lake like this.
橡皮筏
Rubber raft.
西尔维亚布雷克
Sylvia Blake.
这个湖正好适合我
She gave like a cow.
渔猎局的人呢
Who do we have from Fish and Game?
是我
Me.
他是什么人?
Who is this man?
好一座死气沉沉的大湖 看起来几乎停滞
I can see the algae blooms just coming in. Looks almost stagnant.
赫克托·西尔
Hector Cyr.
地球是圆的 你也圆嘟嘟的
Oh, the earth is round and so should you be.
他是谁
Who is he?
你有这里的地形图吗?
I need topographic studies. You got any?
等一下 你不能随便发号施令
Wait a second. You don't just fly in here and start barking orders.
抱歉 我得赶快先进行勘查
I apologize. I just don't want to lose the light when we got time for a quick scout.
你开了吗?
Have you had a little work done?
没有
I have not.
你是谁
Who are you?
赫克托·西尔 我说过
Hector Cyr. I said it once.
让我知道什么时候勘查 好吗?
Let me know when it sinks in, ok?
你看到了吗?
Have you seen it?
没有
No.
对不起 你是来...
Excuse me. You came here to...
帮你找到它
help you find it.
鳄鱼吗
A crocodile?
对
Yeah.
湖水连接海洋
They've been migrating north, you know?
鳄鱼向北迁移
This lake does connect to the ocean.
这是有可能的
It's not as far fetched as it may sound.
鳄鱼是淡水动物
Crocodiles can't swim in saltwater.
你的知识太浅薄了
Yeah, well, that'll be your little secret.
快点 别浪费时间
Come on. We're losing time.
那个猪头干嘛找我碴?
Why did the big one heckle me?
老兄
Hey, pal...
我一定找得到它
If he's close, we'll find him.
这些迹象不会错
Their signatures are unmistakable.
她有没有说我跟她上过床
She tell you that we had sex together?
爽呆了
So vigorous!
我没跟你上过床
I never had sex with you.
我很差劲 女人都没印象
Whew. I'm horrible in bed. They never remember.
天啊
God.
等等
Wait.
停住
Stop!
我好像听到什么
Thought I heard something.
请你原谅我的无知
I don't mean to be discourteous,
鳄鱼怎么会跑到新英格兰
but, uh, how is it a person could come to believe a crocodile is in New England?
它怎么度得了寒冬?
How could it survive winter?
只要鼻孔不结冰就行
Long as their nostrils don't freeze, they survive.
干嘛呀 他连我名字都记不得
Am I foolish to explain things? He had such trouble with my name.
- 赫克托 - 嘿
- Hector. - Hey.
就是这儿吗?
Is this where it happened?
就在这附近
Around here. Yeah.
离大海只有一哩 它游得过来
We're a mile from the ocean. He could've easily made it here.
它得先游到海岸
Assuming he got this far up the seaboard.
巨鳄游得很快
The big ones have been on the move.
我早就说了 谁叫你不听
What have I been telling you? You call me crazy.
赫克托 划浆吧
Hector, just paddle.
亲朋好友怎么劝你都不会听
You know, Sheriff, when friends or family say things, they tend not to register,
那就听陌生人的准没错
so sometimes it helps to hear it from a total stranger.
你太肥了
You're fat.
赫克托 住嘴
Jesus. Hector!
是真的
Oh, yeah.
那是什么
What's that?
What is it?
白鲈鱼群
White perch.
它们在吃东西吗
Are they feeding?
它们不是在吃东西
They aren't feeding.
它们受到惊吓
They're scared.
天啊
Jesus!
快把腿跨上来
Get your legs out of the water.
别乱动
Don't move your legs.
开玩笑的吧?
Are you kidding me?
腿要伸直
Keep your legs still.
走开
Get off!
去左边
Hector, to the left.
到后面去
Move it left!
快划 快划
Paddle, paddle!
我们什么也没看到
No one actually saw anything.
是的 我了解
Yes, I realize that, sir,
船被翻过来应该不会是海獭干的
but something flipped us over, and I doubt very much if it was a mink.
我是博物馆派来的古生物学家
I am a paleontologist. I work for a natural history museum.
怎么样
I am not some--
他们不相信她
They don't believe her.
谢了
Thank you.
你们在浪费纳税人的钱王八蛋
It's so rewarding to imagine my tax dollar finding its way to you, you fuck-shit!
你真辣
You're a saucy flirt.
你说得对
You were right.
野生动物保护局不肯派人来
U.S.Wildlife won't send anybody without a confirmation.
用不着他们
We don't need 'em.
怎样?
Yeah?
你最好过来看看
Might wanna come take a look at this.
我的天
Oh, my God.
蛆
Worms.
我最讨厌蛆了
Oh, I gotta thing about worms.
那是人的脚趾
It's a human toe.
有点腐烂 有黏液
Some decomposition, a little acidic--
肯定是被吞食过
definitely been swallowed.
这就是死者吗?
Is this the man who was killed?
他比较高大
He seemed taller.
唷
Phew.
是鳄鱼没错 它们是关键动物
You got a croc, all right. They're a keystone species.
他又掉书袋子吗?
Did he just explain something?
关键动物影响整个生态系统
Keystone species effects the whole ecosystem.
所以才引来蛆和鲈鱼
That would explain these worms and those perch.
这是只鳄鱼
We got a crocodile.
这是你的朋友
Here's your friend.
# It's not unusual #
# To be loved by anyone #
# To have fun with anyone #
# But when I see you hangin' around #
# With anyone #
# It's not unusual... #
他付我们钱
He paid us.
五百块钱
500.
这是个陷阱
It's a trap.
你们收他的钱
You accepted money from him?
我们收的是支票
We took a check.
# When I see you out and about #
当警察很危险 对吧
Law enforcement is very dangerous work, isn't it?
你的咪咪好大哦
And you have such big, wonderful boobs.
谢谢夸奖
Ha ha. Thank you.
# It's not unusual #
# It happens every day #
嘿
Hey!
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey! - Hey!
你们是来执勤
We're here on official business.
不是来玩的
This is not a party.
你来了就不好玩
Yeah, but now that you're here...
闭嘴
Quiet!
你挖洞干嘛?
What's with digging the holes?
鳄鱼很大胆
Well, crocodiles are--are very brazen.
喜欢到陆地 也受声言吸引
They like to come on land, and of course they're attracted to noise.
大家都回自己的帐蓬去
Everybody out! Back to your tents!
快
Now!
她能不能留下来
Oh, could she stay?
我们...我们打算做爱
We were...we were hoping to mate.
不行
No.
出去
Out.
你给我听好
Now, you listen...
你在惹我 我会把你踢回姥姥家
If it were up to me, you'd be on your way home.
但是 我说了算
But I'm not in charge.
那里有个伟大发现
That's a shocker there.
给我仔细听着
I'm going to say this
我很老实 有话都直说
because I believe in being straight with people.
我觉得你是个神经病
I think you are a mental.
警长
Sheriff...
谢谢你这么诚实
I appreciate your candor. Really, I do.
知道别人的想法总是好的
I think it's always good to know where somebody's coming from,
不过你好像没什么想法
and, frankly, your origins have been a bit of a mystery to me.
湖面好平
Look how flat that water is.
一颗石子可以跳十下
You could get 10 skips on a good one, easy.
什么?
Sorry?
打水瓢子呀
Skipping stones.
暑假我都到爷爷的湖畔小屋
Growing up, I used to summer at my grandparents' place on a lake like this.
整天都在打水瓢子
I'd skip stones all day.
每次都赢别的小孩
Beat playing with the other kids.
我相信也是
I'm sure it did.
明天你最好留在岸上
Look, I think it's best if you stayed on shore a while.
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
我不想跟你吵
I'm not trying to pick a fight,
不过那玩意弄翻了船
but whatever's out there did flip a canoe.
我才不要留在岸上
I am not staying on shore.
太危险了
It's dangerous.
我不是大老远跑来露营的
No, I didn't fly up here just to roast marshmallows.
你为什么要来
Why did you fly up here?
- 听着 - 古生物学家不会跑来抓鳄鱼
- Look. - paleontologists are not sent to Maine to hunt for crocodiles.
我是来看那伙牙齿
I was sent up here to look at the tooth.
你看过了牙齿
You looked at the tooth.
你到底来干什么
What are you doing out here?
我跟上司谈恋爱
I was dating my boss...
后来他泡上我的好友甩掉我
and he turned out to be involved with a coworker who was also my friend.
所以他故意派我到缅因州
And for the sake of comfort--theirs--I was shipped off to Maine.
我还不想回去
And I don't feel like going back yet.
这是真的
I'm not making it up.
你大可以留在镇上不必跑来这里
Still, you don't have to stay out here. I mean, you can stay in town.
我来都来了 我才不走除非这儿有虱子
I've come. I'm here. I'm staying...unless there are ticks.
我了解鳄鱼
I know crocodiles.
放心 我不会碍着你
And I won't get in your way.
我只想参一脚
I just really do want to be a part of this.
七点整出发
7:00 A.M.?
谢谢
Thank you.
晚安
Good night.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我的妈呀
Jesus fucking Christ!
你在搞什么鬼
Ohh. What the hell are you doing?
你在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?!
谁叫你躲在这儿
Oh, Jesus. You clowning around?
我正在装陷阱
I'm laying a spring trap!
陷阱?
A spring trap?
我不是说鳄鱼会跑到陆地上来
I keep telling you they can come on land you know.
你不想在半夜惊醒吧
You don't want to wake up in the middle of the night.
我差点向你开枪
I could've shot you.
这可能会救你一命
This could end up saving your life, which is meaningful for you,
不过你这么蠢也许我不应该救你
because the more you live, the more sex you get to have with your sister!
怎么回事
What's going on?
他带着手枪小便 他像蟑娜一样爬来爬去
He's crawling around like a cockroach here.
我不管他多么有钱
I don't care how much money--
他拿枪指住我
He's waving his little wang around!
把我吓个半死
He's scaring the shit out of me!
够了
All right, all right!
我只说一遍
I'll say this once.
谢谢你带来的精密装备
Your fancy equipment aside, which we appreciate--
不过你捣蛋就得走人
if you interfere, you're gone.
就这么简单
Simple as that.
这家伙真的秀逗了
How much of a wacko is this guy?
赫克托把鳄鱼看得很重要
Well...the thing about Hector is he takes this crocodile business very...
噢 老兄
Oh, man.
他认为鳄鱼是神
He thinks they're godly.
是什么
What was that?
每个原始文化都把鳄鱼神化
In his defense, every primitive culture known to man deified them.
中国 埃及 澳洲 亚洲
Ancient China, Egypt, Australia, Asia.
鳄鱼被崇拜的次数比耶稣还多
Going back in history, crocodiles have been more worshipped than Jesus.
所以我得把他当真吗?
Is this supposed to make us take him more seriously?
不 你得了解他的想法
No, it's supposed to make you understand him.
他是神话学教授他相信鳄鱼很神圣
He's a mythology professor. He believes that they're divine conduits.
他找得到它 我们就忍着点
And he can find them, so we should try to put up with him.
他是个疯子
He's a fruitcake.
大家都去睡吧
We should get some sleep.
该死
Damn it!
他也是个好猎人
And he's a good trapper.
鳄鱼听到就会有反应
We can expect a quick response if he hears that.
成鳄听到幼鳄声就会攻击
Adult crocs will move on distressed hatchlings.
我不想问些幼稚问题不过要是这真是只鳄鱼
Again, I don't mean to be annoying with my questions but if it is a crocodile, which I don't think it is,
如果它听到幼鳄声会攻击你
and they do charge these baby hatchling sounds,
为什么还要到水底?
why exactly would you want to be underwater at the time?
这个人去就很合理了
With you, it makes sense.
鳄鱼是不会在水底攻击
You see, Sheriff, the thing is, they don't really attack underwater.
那家伙在水底被吃掉
That Walt guy got hit underwater.
鳄鱼在水底也看不见
True. They don't see that well underwater.
它们的眼睛上面有一层瞬膜
They have nictitating lenses over their eyes...
停下
Burke, stop here.
- 现在? - 嗯
- Now? - Yeah.
只要被鳄鱼盯上就潜到水底
...You dive underwater
- 它们看不到你 - 它们闻得到
- and they probably won't be able to see you. - They can smell.
好了 我们得干活了
I hate to interrupt but we got work to do.
讲话总可以吧
Hey, we can talk if we want.
可以讲话
Yeah, we can talk if we want.
请你把锚放下去
Would you mind putting down the anchor?
我们一下去就打开来
Wait till we're down there before you turn that thing on.
好的
Got it.
走吧 赫克托
Let's go, Hector.
祝好运
Good luck.
我带了猪肉当护身符
I brought a pork chop for luck.
你最好挂在脖子上
Maybe you can hang it around your neck.
你真好心
That's sweet.
待会我再让你替我服务
Maybe later you can chew the bark off my big, fat log.
那是搞基暗示吗
Was that, like, a homosexual remark?
别问我
Don't ask me.
他一定是个疯子
Could be a mental.
不过有钱的疯子被称为怪人
I heard if a mental person is rich enough, they just call him eccentric.
他不是疯子
He's not mental.
他是鳄鱼专家
He's seen every crocodile in the world.
他跟食人鳄游泳都没被咬过
He even swam in the Grametti with killer Niles. He never got nipped.
所以他才把鳄鱼当成神
And that's why he thinks they're godly--
只是因为没被咬过?
'Cause they don't bite him?
我不知道
I don't know.
他说他相信鳄鱼的眼睛
He said he knew it when he looked in their eyes.
那是鱼龙之眼
"Eyes of a Dragon."
有鳄鱼才怪呢
So much for crocodiles.
它大概在陆地上
It's probably on land.
是啊
Yeah, right.
那是什么
What was that?
不晓得
I don't know.
可恶
Shit.
锚被什么勾住了
Hey! Something's got the anchor line!
快割断它
Untie it! Untie the line!
我在试
I'm trying!
快
Hurry!
快割断它
Cut the line!
好
Right!
糟糕
Shit!
快点
Come on.
怎么回事
What happened?
不知道
I don't know.
快点呀
Hurry. Hurry up.
它一定把锚放掉了
Must've just let go.
快发动啊
Come on.
糟糕 警长
Shit! Hurry!
汉克
Hank!
好了
Ok!
噢
Oh!
快点!
Hurry!
Hurry.
小心 它就在下面
My God, it's right under you!
老天
Aah! Oh, Christ.
快上船
Come on, get in the boat.
你没事吧?
You all right?
嗯
Yeah.
赫克托呢
Where's Hector?
不知道
I lost track.
我们分散开来
We went different directions.
那边有水泡
There's some bubbles over there.
拖上来
Pull it up.
把他拖上来
All right. Come on. Bring him aboard.
怎么回事
What's happened?
快点
Come on.
- 你们看到了? - 我看见了一个东西
- You see it? - We saw something.
- 多大? - 闭嘴 赶紧上来
- How big is it? - Shut up and get on board.
把声纳拉上来
We lost track of it. Burke, pull up the speaker!
你没事吧
Are you all right?
- 启动引擎 - 啊
- Grab him! - Aah!
拉他上来
Pull him in!
好了吗
That it?
好了
Yeah.
发生得太快 没有人看到
Nobody actually saw it. It happened suddenly.
不是被船桨绞死的吗
Didn't get caught in the outboard?
不是
It wasn't the outboard.
叫他们尽快赶来
Tell them to get here fast, huh?
你没事吧
You OK?
凯莉
Kelly?
没事
Yeah.
谁都没看见吗
Nobody saw anything.
没有
No.
野生动物保护局正派人来
U.S. Wildlife's on their way.
警方要封锁一切的消息
The police want to keep everything quiet so the press doesn't get wind of anything.
大家都要我们...
Everybody just wants us to...
按兵不动
"Sit tight."
你真的没事吗
Are you...ok?
呃...
Well...
你知道
you know...
真的
Yeah.
警长 我
Well, Sheriff, I'm, uh...
为你的手下感到遗憾
Very sorry about your deputy.
他是个好人吗
He was a good man?
是
Yep.
只要有人丧命
Whenever somebody dies, I...
我没能认识他就会感到难过
I always think that it's such a waste that I didn't know them any better.
很遗憾你没认识
Sorry for your loss, Hector.
我不是这个意思
Not really what I meant.
他的头被咬掉
Head was just...bitten off.
我以前常梦到我没有头
You know, I used to have a recurring nightmare that I was headless.
我在地上看着无头的身体
I'd be down on the ground looking up at my body, no head,
到处跌跌撞撞
just walking around bumping into everything.
我父母不肯让我走屋
And my parents...wouldn't let me in the house.
他们怕我撞坏新买的古董台灯
Because they just bought all these antique lamps,
而且他们不希望我去打扰他们 王八蛋
and they didn't want me to knock them over, the fuckers.
邻居小孩觉得我的头像一颗球
Then the neighborhood bullies, they'd see my round head on the ground looking like a ball,
于是就把它当足球踢
and they'd come over, and they'd start a soccer game.
我的头被踢来踢去
And as I was being kicked around,
我却很高兴能跟他们一起玩
I'd actually just feel grateful for being allowed in the game.
你觉得怎样?
What are-- what are your thoughts?
你知道吗
You know, Hector...
我相信你应该是个好疯子
I'm sure you're a fine person in your own mental way,
我想你最好别跟我讲话
but I think it would be best if you and I didn't speak.
野生动物保护局几时才来
When is U.S. Wildlife getting here?
我还在等消息
I'm still waiting to confirm if they...
噢 天
Oh, Jesus.
我可以把他救下来
I--I could probably cut him down,
不过他的表情有点古怪
but there's this odd look of mayhem on his upside-down face.
汉克
Hank.
什么?
Yes?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
可以救我下来吗
Could you cut me down?
答应我你不能伤害我
Do you promise that you won't attempt to injure me?
我连看都不想看你一眼
I have no interest in ever looking at you, Hector.
好吧
Ok.
直接把他拉下来就行
Just, uh, pull him down. It's a counterweight.
我去拿刀子
Here. I'll get the knife.
如果我记得有陷阱就不会让你去
If I'd remembered it was there, I never would've let you walk that way.
没事了
All right. It's over.
没事了 记得吗
It's over. Remember?
你答应不伤害他
You promised not to hurt him, so...
我说谎
I lied.
等等 嘿
Wait. Hey! Hey!
住手 住手
Come on! Hold up!
你无处可逃了
Nowhere to go, my friend.
别闹了
Now, just--come on! Knock it off!.
快放下来
Knock it off. Put that down.
冷静点
Just settle...
小心
Jesus! Look out!
哇
Whoa!
操
Aw, shit!
好吧
Ok.
我承认
I admit it.
那是只鳄鱼
It's a crocodile.
它是印度太平洋鳄
He's an lndo-Pacific.
鳞片是椭圆形 是亚洲鳄
Scales were oval. He's an Asian crocodile.
它为什么会跑来这儿?
Why would he come here? It's impossible.
亚洲 它是怎么来的?
Asia. How would he get here?
香港有个猪头把它冲下马桶
Obviously some asshole in Hong Kong flushed him down the toilet.
它一定有三十尺长
He was 30 feet, right? Had to be.
幸好我带了一把大枪
Well, now maybe somebody's happy I brought my big gun.
你要把它轰死吗
Oh you're gonna blow him away now?
当然了
I should think so.
用大炮把它轰死
With your cannon?
是啊 不应该吗
Right. What, I shouldn't?
- 它是大自然的奇迹 - 但是它很可怖
- Well, he's a miracle of nature, - but I know he's very scary.
你才是大自然的奇迹
You're the miracle of nature.
够了 冷静点
Guys, guys, easy, easy.
今晚什么也不能做
We're not gonna do anything tonight.
我不知道鳄鱼能横越大海
I never heard of a crocodile crossing an ocean.
这是书本上的知识
Well, they conceal information like that in books.
好了
All right, pal!
冷静点
Hey, hey. hey-
放开他
No, no. Let him go.
我也受不了他
I'm sick of him, too.
我得警告你
I do need to warn you, Sheriff.
我家很有钱
The thing about being rich,
我从小就被送去学空手道
my parents did have the added luxury of ditching me off at karate school
我是棕带高手
on a regular basis, so I am a brown belt.
尽管来吧
Go ahead. Take your best shot.
汉克
Hank!
他说他会空手道
He said he knew karate.
你打他
You hit him.
没错
I did, yeah.
来
Here.
他有说开始吗
Did he say "go"?
比试前不都要先说开始吗
Aren't you supposed to say "go" in karate?
他应该说开始的
You're supposed to say "go."
离他远一点
Hank, just keep your distance from him.
赫克托 回你的帐篷去
Hector, go to your tent. Cool down.
他没有回答我
He doesn't answer my questions?
你怎么不回答?
Why don't you answer my questions?
要是我撞到树一定会说开始
I fall into a hole. I go up in a tree.
我发誓 我会说开始
I swear to God, I'll say "go."
先鞠躬再说开始
You bow, and then you say "go."
你去死吧
As in "go fuck yourself."
他们好像小孩子
Jesus. They're just like children.
是啊
Yeah.
老天
Oh, my God.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
我没事
Yeah, I'm all right.
我有急救箱
I've got something for that.
让我来弄
I can fix that.
真的吗
Yeah?
真的
Yeah.
我得绑紧一点
I just gotta pull it a little tighter.
好了
There we go.
这是谁教你的?
Who taught you to be a nurse?
我爸是外科医生
Father's a surgeon.
我还会缝合 其实这样最好
I can even stitch in a pinch, which probably wouldn't be such a bad idea on this.
不用了
Uh, no, thanks.
好吧
Ok.
鳄鱼跳出来你的表情好逗
You should have seen the look on your face when that croc jumped out.
你看到熊的表情吗?
You see the look on the bear?
就是那个表情
That was the look.
我不知道
I don't know.
大自然法则可能改变了那玩意真是...
The laws of nature could be changing, Jack.That thing out there, that's--
你玩得很开心 对吧?
You're having the best time of your life, aren't you?
什么?
What?
有人被咬死耶
What? People have been killed.
我并不开心
I hardly think I'm having a good time.
你怎么能
Why would you--
这么明显吗
Does it show?
这是我第一次真正冒险
This is the first time I've ever actually...you know, been in the middle of anything.
你就是想要来冒险吗?
Is that why you're here, to get in the middle of something?
也许吧
Maybe.
我老是读一些冒险故事而却没有...
I've always read about what's happened. I've never...
我们应该上床了
We should go to bed.
我是说该去休息了
I mean we should go to, uh... rest.
各自回帐篷休息
We should go to our separate tents,
我有一些
and--here-- get some--go.
谢了
I got it.
谢谢你帮我包扎伤口
Thanks for the bandage.
晚安
Night.
Yeah.
迅雷不及掩耳
It doesn't even see him.
看 它成功了
There, he got it.
它只有一个天敌
He has one natural enemy.
只有一个
Only one.
人类
Man?
Man.
你是专家
So you're the big expert.
这玩意是变种吗
You think ours is some kind of mutant or---
不一定 印度也有三十尺巨鳄
Not necessarily. There's a 30-footer in India.
被猎杀最大的记录是27尺
Biggest one ever killed on record was 27 feet.
它为什么跑来这里?
So why is he here?
老实说
Honestly...
我不知道
I don't know.
要提高警觉
Keep your eyes peeled.
鳄鱼的动作是很快
You know how fast these things can be.
我身上有虱子
I've got ticks, I know it.
虱子特别喜欢我
They're just so drawn to me. I gotta thing about ticks.
钻进我的头发和皮肤里
Crawling up your pant leg. Put their heads under your skin.
你们看
Look.
什么?
What?
杰克
Jack.
好大的足印
That's a pretty big print.
你飞得越来越低
Seems like we're getting lower.
因为我要降落
That's what happens when I land.
为什么
Why are we landing?
这显然是它住的洞穴
Because this is the cove that he obviously lives in.
你干嘛降落?
So why are we landing?
赫克托
Hector!
可以拓下来吗
We can lift it?
也许可以
Maybe.
别把它弄糊
Don't want to mush it there.
才没有
I'm not mushing it.
别那么用力 太软了
You might mush it. It's a little soft.
拜托 我才没有用力
For Christ's sake, I'm not mushing it!
老天爷
Oh, God.
好
Ok.
我受够了
That is it! That is it!
不 不 我碰到头了
No, no, I keep getting hit with heads!
冷静点 好吗?
Try to calm down.
你才冷静点
You calm down!
冷静点 深呼吸
Calm down, ok? Just keep breathing.
我很冷静 我很镇定
I'm being very calm! I am composed!
这是我第二次被断头打到
This is the second time I've been hit with a severed head,and it upsets me!
搞什么...
What the hell?
我只想回帐篷去
I just want to go back to my tent now.
可以回去吗?
Can we please go back?
别开玩笑
You gotta be kidding.
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding!
你看
Look.
# The itsy-bitsy spider #
# Crawled up the water spout #
我的天
# Down comes the rain #
# To wash the spider out? #
她在干嘛
What is she doing?
# Dum de dum de dum #
噢
Oh.
什么?
What?
注意看水边十尺处
Look 10 feet into the water.
快来吃哟
Come and get it!
哇
Wow.
令人作呕
Disgusting.
我又没有犯法
I haven't broken any laws.
你有犯法
Oh, but you have, ma'am.
你欺骗警察
You lied to us.
那是妨碍公务
That can be obstruction of justice.
你害一个人被咬死
A man has been killed, in part because of your silence.
我可以告你蓄意危害他人
I could make out a charge of reckless endangerment.
你拿牛去喂鳄鱼也是不对的
And I'm sure PETA would be annoyed at how you treat your cows.
我要是老实说你就会去猎杀它
The reason I lied, if I told you the truth, you'd hunt it down and kill it,
这不就是你所要做的吗
which seems to be exactly what you're trying to do.
你喂这只巨鳄有多久了
How long have you been feeding this thing?
六年了
6 years.
六年?
6 years?
柏尼去钓鱼 它就跟着回来
Well, Bernie was out fishing, and it followed him home.
我们拿东西喂它 它又没害人
So we threw it some scraps, and, well, he didn't seem to bother anybody.
它就像是野生的宠物
He became kind of like a pet who lives in the wild.
他就这么出现了?
He just appeared?
你不知道它是怎么来的
You have no idea how he arrived here?
不知道 你知道吗
No. Do you?
你不是把柏尼推去喂鳄鱼吧
Your husband Bernie, you didn't, by any chance, lead him to the lake blindfolded?
你再乱讲我就要你好看
If I had a dick, this is where I'd tell you to suck it.
你先生是被巨鳄吃掉吗
Did the crocodile kill your husband?
是 不过那是个错误
Yes, but it was all...it was a mistake.
错误?
A mistake?
两年前一匹马挣脱缰绳
One of our horses got loose 2 years ago.
跑去湖边喝水
Went to the lake to drink,
巨鳄想吃它 柏尼去拦它
and the crocodile started coming in, and Bernie went to intercede, and--
要是我报警它一定没命
if I'd reported it, they'd have sent people to kill it.
你怎么能不报警?
Ma'am, how could you not report this?
这会害死人
It puts human life at risk.
湖边没人烟
Nobody lives on this lake.
这是它的湖
It's really his lake now.
我知道你疯了 不过别下去
Come on, Hector. I know you're crazy, but you can't do this.
我得看看它的鳄窝
I need to see his habitat up close, Deputy Gare.
看"动物奇观"嘛
Then watch Nova, ok?
别下水
But don't go in the water.
求求你
Please.
我跟你上床
I'll have sex with you.
快走吧
Let's just get out of here.
亲爱的
Darling,
它不会伤害我的
he's not gonna hurt me.
别去
Don't.
赫克托
Hector!
犯罪率这么高 飞机老是失事
Murders and rapes in the cities. People bomb planes.
警察也没办法
Can the police stop them? No.
我只是用小牛喂一只鳄鱼
But feed one little cow to a crocodile--
你被软禁了 乖乖等警察来
You stay right here until the police show. You're under full house arrest.
谢了...
Thank you...
蠢警长
Officer Fuckmeat.
警长 赫克托有麻烦
Sheriff, we gotta problem with Hector.
什么麻烦
What problem?
他潜下去了
He went swimming.
收到
Check.
我突然觉得自己很蠢
Suddenly I feel a bit foolish here.
你跟别的鳄鱼不同
You're different from the others.
我的天
Holy Spirit of Sobek.
我的妈呀
Holy Ghost.
他妈的
Holy shit.
赫克托
Hector!
赶快启动引擎
Just turn the ignition.
很容易
It's fuel injected.
快点
Come on!
我知道咬断我的头很爽
I know that under the circumstances, biting my head off might seem viable.
不过你没这么贱吧
It would cheapen you.
我用枪打它
I may get a shot!
不行
No!
子弹打不穿它
Bullets might not penetrate its hide.
天啊 加油 再游过来一点
Oh, Jesus. All right, just a little further.
就像这样
Just like that.
快走
Move over!
Go!
- 快飞 - 我正在试
- "Go! - I'm trying.
天啊
Ahh! Jesus!
鳄鱼先生 你这次太过份
That's your last little stunt, Mr. Crocodile.
你被禁足了
You're grounded.
这些可是精密的装备
This is some very delicate equipment that you're throwing around.
我不管 你想自杀 是吗
I don't care. You trying to kill yourself?.
你想去见你老伴 对吗
You want to meet your maker, is that it?
你想跟鱼神游泳是你家的事
You might think they're godly,you might get some spiritual lift out of backstroking with dragons,
不过你差点害死一名警员
but you just put a deputy at risk out there, sir.
可是它没把我吃掉
Let's not overlook the fact that he didn't eat me.
因为它刚吃了一头牛
'Cause he just ate a cow, stupid.
我是平民 不是赙鱼
I'm a civilian. I'm not a trout.
你根本管不着我
You have no authority over me whatsoever.
我可以逮捕你
Hey, hey, I can arrest you.
那就动手呀
Well, then do it.
你伤了他的自尊心
You hurt his feelings.
我不在乎 你在乎吗
I don't care. Do you care?
不在乎 他是个混球
No. He's an asshole.
你想被它吃掉吗
Did you want to be killed by it?
你真以为我疯了吗?
You think I'm that nuts?
赫克托
Hector.
你这种行为等于是自杀
What you just did, there had to be at least some sort of a death wish going on.
在古美拉尼西亚
In ancient Melanesia,
嫌犯都被丢进鳄鱼池
people suspected of crimes would be thrown to the crocodiles.
鳄鱼们会判定什么人有罪
Crocodiles would decide. They would be the judge.
你想受到审判吗
Oh, and so that was you wanting to be judged out there?
也许吧 又怎样
Maybe I was, and so what?
很没道理吗?
Is that too arbitrary?
总比当个有钱人好吧
Better to be measured by my wealth?
总比被别人讨着要钱好吧
Better for me to get my self-esteem looking in the eyes of cheap sycophants craving a meal ticket?
鱼龙眼里有诚实
There was more honesty in those dragon's eyes.
鱼龙眼里有尊严
There was more dignity in those dragon's eyes.
老天爷 废话少说
Jesus, Hector, cut the shit.
是啊 管它的
Aw, fuck it.
你答应不再下水了?
So, can I tell them you won't go back in the water?
是啊 我答应不再下水
Oh, yeah, sure. I'm not going back in the water.
我不可能再下水了
No way I'm going back in the water.
好吧
OK.
凯莉
Kelly.
别让他们杀死它
We can't let 'em kill it.
好 收拾一下 准备走
Yeah, pull all the trucks in and start packing.
全部吗
Everything?
对
Yeah.
好
All right.
我会通知他们 佛州渔猎局三个钟头后到
Just heard from Wildlife and Florida Fish and Game. They're gonna be here in 3 hours.
好吧
Ok.
我们最好收拾走人
So we might as well pack up.
好主意
Good idea.
他们会猎捕它吗
Will they try to trap him?
什么?
Sorry?
佛州渔猎局会怎么对付它
Florida Fish and Game. What'll they do when they get here?
告诉她呀
Tell her, Jack.
用渔网抓不到它
Won't be able to snag him in pitments, right?
它在水底被麻醉会淹死
And you tranq him in the water, and he drowns.
他们可以在陆地上麻醉它
They could try to tranq him on land.
他们不会这么做
Oh, sure, they could, but they won't.
它伤了人命
He's taken human life.
肯定活不了
The mission will be to put him down.
是真的吗
Is that true?
捕不到三十尺以上的巨鳄
They've never been able to trap anything 30 feet.
他们得试试看
But they have to try, right?
它会被带到哪儿 佛州?
Where are they gonna take him, Florida?
亚洲吗?
Back to Asia?
我有足够的麻醉药能...
I got enough flaxedil with me to put him out--
- 制伏它 - 想都别想 不可以
- and I think I know a way - Forget it.
- 听我说 - 不可以
- Jack, hear me out. - Forget it.
我知道我是个有钱的疯子
I know I'm a fat, rich, nut fuck, whacko who's about as grounded as a street pigeon,
继续说
Keep going.
这是罕见的巨鳄
But this thing...
这里
Here?
来到缅因州
Maine?
三十尺长
30 feet?
你不认为这是个奇迹吗
Don't you think we're dealing with a bit of a miracle?
能活抓它才是个奇迹
Yeah. The miracle would be to take him alive.
要是能制伏它?
Yeah, but if we could neutralize him--
该怎么制伏它?
How are we gonna neutralize him?
把它引到陆地再打麻醉枪
Lure him on land and pump him full of drugs.
好
Oh, right.
波特兰有座空油缸
I know of an empty oil tank in Portland.
可以把它养在那儿
If we drugged him, we could contain him there.
它有一百五十岁
He's 150 years old.
大概从亚洲游到缅因州
He probably swam here from another continent. He's migrated to Maine.
它迁移到这儿 怎么能杀它
How the hell do we say we just kill it?
这只巨鳄是生态环境的奇迹
Jack, this thing being here does have some ecological significance.
你必须保护濒临绝种动物
And you are in the business of protecting things against extinction.
我也得保护警员
Including deputies.
我了解
I understand that,
但我们能活抓它
but if it's possible to take him alive--
不可能
No, it's not possible.
它都猎食动物
Look, he follows anything that moves, right?
在岸上放诱饵 我有大渔网
We set a trap on the beach. I got enough net--
不行 绝对网不住它
No. There's no net that's gonna hold him.
只要等麻醉药生效就行
It'll keep him tangled long enough for the drugs to kick in.
二十多尺的巨鳄都被活抓过
For God's sake, Jack, they've trapped crocs bigger than 20 feet.
这并非不可能
This is not completely out of the question.
你知道 这是可行的
It's possible, and you know that.
你也知道佛州的人会杀死它
And those fucks from Florida won't even try, and you know that, too.
我有麻醉药 他有一把大枪
I got the drugs. He's got a big cannon if anything goes wrong.
该怎么引诱它?
How do you get him to the net?
要毕太太叫它吗
Ask Mrs. Bickerman to call him?
你们拿着麻醉枪站在卡车上
You guys can be in the trucks with the tranq guns.
它一攻击就开车
If he charges, you take off.
它跑不过你
He's not that fast.
试一试无妨
We just have to try.
只试一次就行
One try. Just one try.
我们该怎么诱它上岸
Like Hank says, how would we lure him in?
我会告你的
I'll sue you!
尽管告
Go ahead.
你不能抢走我的牛
You can't take a cow by eminent domain!
当然能
We just did!
它不会受伤的
We won't let her get hurt, ma'am.
你们全是王八蛋
You're all cocksuckers!
我早就知道了
I knew at first. I just didn't want to say it.
我们很有把握
We know what we're doing.
牛被吊在直升机上
We got a cow hanging from a helicopter.
没什么风
Not much drag.
它不晃动就没事
As long as I can keep her from swinging, we're ok.
这么做是对的
We're doing the right thing.
等你进了鳄鱼肚就会后悔
You might feel different if you get eaten.
是啊 谢了
Yeah, thanks.
大家都有麻醉枪
Tranq gun with every rifle.
射程越远越好
That's as far back as it goes, right?
赫克托 别让牛下水
All right Hector, keep enough tension to hold her up.
谁知道它会不会游泳
We don't know how well she can swim.
是啊
Right.
我不想说
I hate to say it.
不过它越晃动越好
The more she thrashes, the better.
你们准备好了吗
You ready on shore?
我们准备好了
Yeah, we're all right. We're ready.
好了
Ok.
牛累了就把它拉上来
If she gets tired, pull her out.
它在干什么?
What's she doing now?
它想要飞
She's trying to fly.
这头牛很不爽
This is not a happy cow.
我希望巨鳄把你朋友全吃掉
I'm rooting for the crocodile. I hope he swallows your friends whole.
你尽管来逮捕我吧
You might want to arrest me for that, too.
希望警察被吃掉犯法吗
Is that a crime--To wish the chewing of law enforcement?
我不确定
I'm not sure, ma'am.
你抓到他了?
You got 'em?
这里
Yeah, over here.
在那儿
Little battery!
怎么回事
What's the deal?
我们试过了
Well, we tried.
再等一下子
Just a little longer, please.
它好像没在游泳
She doesn't seem to be swimming.
它像个大茶包被泡在水里
No, she's floating. She looks like a giant tea bag.
赫克托
Ok, Hector.
没有动静 没戏唱了
Good plan, bad bait. Game's up.
这头牛真令人失望
The cow disappoints me.
等一下
Hold on.
有动静了
I got something on the screen.
有什么
What do you got?
它来了
He's coming.
在哪儿
Where?
有多远
How far out?
大约三十米
30 meters or so.
它很慢 不过正游过来
He's moving slow, but he's definitely coming.
可以看到吗或只是雷达讯号
Can you confirm visually or just radar?
是雷达讯号
Radar.
它在水底但往这儿过来
He's underwater, but he is coming!
大伙儿上卡车
All right, everybody back in the trucks!
快点 快点
Move, move, move!
我们走 我们走
Let's go, let's go!
我们走
Let's go!
把它引过来
Lead him in.
来了
On our way.
大家要瞄准腹部和侧面
Remember to aim for the stomach and the sides!
麻醉针穿不过鳄背
These darts won't pierce his back!
它浮出来了
He's surfacing. There's his snout.
在那儿
There he is!
看到它了
We've spotted him, Hector.
你这小家伙
You little snacker.
太靠近就把牛拉起来
If he gets near her, pull up.
她担心牛的安全
She's worried about the cow now.
慢慢来
Nice and slow, Hector.
他的网子最好有用
This net thing better work.
你不是被网过吗
He got you with it.
它在水下四尺
We're in about 4 feet of water now.
它在叫耶
She's mooing.
你不会叫吗?
You wouldn't?
它也在乱踢
She's also kicking.
再靠近点
A little closer, Hector.
糟了
Oh, shit.
小心
Watch out!
王八蛋
Motherfucker!
可恶
Shit!
他人呢
Where is he?
我们得去救他
We gotta get to him.
支援我们
Back us up.
放下麻醉枪 用来福枪
Lose the tranq guns. go to the rifles.
用来福枪
Get the rifles!
它在哪里
Where'd he go?
等等
Hold up.
别下水
Don't go back into the water.
瞄准了就开枪
If you get a safe shot, take it.
赫克托 别动
Do not move, Hector!
你看到什么吗
Can you see anything from out there?
没有
Nothing!
也许它游走了
Maybe he swam back out!
天
Jesus!
赫克托
Hector!
嘿
Hey!
快回到卡车上
Get back in the truck!
我掩护他
I got him covered.
它在哪里
Where is he?
不知道
I don't know.
它潜到水底
He's gone under.
我现在觉得很安全
I just have this feeling everything's totally safe.
- 在那儿 - 它游走了
- There! - He's swimming out!
我看到它了 我看到它的尾巴
I think I see him! I think I see his tail!
糟了 凯莉
Shit! Kelly!
凯莉!
Kelly!
快游过来
Kelly, swim, swim to me!
快游到我这边
Swim to me, Kelly!
快开枪呀
Shoot the fucking thing!
我瞄不准
I don't have a clean shot.
潜下去
Dive under!
Go under!
操
Fuck.
让我们来拯救它
"Let's save him."
活抓它真是烂点子
What a fucking great idea.
来
Come on.
Here.
上来
Here we go.
它在哪里
Where is he?
不知道
I don't know.
看不到它
We can't see him.
什么
What--What?
赫克托
Hector!
好吧
All right.
它玩完了
Game over.
看
Look.
它很痛苦
He's suffering.
我让它安乐死
I get to be humane.
不行...
No, no!
它被困住了
No, no, no, look, he's trapped!
我们成功了
We've done it!
不是被网住 不过它动不了
So what? It's not a net, but he's trapped.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
杀死它
Shoot him.
我还有麻醉药 它半死不活
I got more drugs. He's half dead.
它还活着 开枪
He's half alive. Shoot him!
麻醉药生效了
The drugs are kicking in.
看看它
Look at him.
它完了
He's done.
汉克 开枪吧
Hank.
大家退后
All right, stand back.
不 警长
No, no, no, Sheriff I.
你看
Look.
你看 你看
Look, look.
它动弹不得
He's got nothing left.
向它开枪吧
Go ahead. Shoot him.
真的吗
Really?
- 杰克 我们... - 凯莉
- Jack, we don't-- - Kelly.
你不必杀死它 该死的 看看它
We don't have to destroy him! God damn it, look at him!
给我吧
Let me have that.
它被制伏了
He's been neutralized.
别这样 它被困住了
Come on, Jack, he's trapped!
看看它 它动也不能动
Look at him! He can't move!
- 看看它 - 何必杀它呢?
- Look at him! - What's the point?
你没必要杀它的
We don't have to do this.
求求你 别杀它
Jack, you don't have to. Please!
天啊
Oh, God!
我死定了
He's got me!
天啊
Jesus!
Jesus Christ!
有两只巨鳄
Are there 2? I think there's 2.
我看到了
I can see that.
它咬我
He bit me!
它咬我 有两只耶
He bit me! There's 2, there's 2!
我会数
I can count.
不
No!
又变成一只了
Back to one.
来吧
Go ahead.
绑起来
Flax him.
他们总算来了
Oh, here they are.
来的正是时候 你们好啊
Just in time. Nice to see you.
你们得替这只鳄鱼治伤
We're gonna need to get this reptile some medical attention.
我们用直升机困住它
We, uh...trapped him with our chopper.
波特兰
Portland?
对 到波特兰
Yes, Portland.
到那儿再想办法安置它
They'll tank him there until we figure out something better to do.
警长
So, Sheriff, Sheriff,
你轰掉巨鳄
you got to fire your big gun finally.
爽吗
Was it fun?
没那么爽
Overrated.
毕太太怎么说?
What'd Bickerman say?
她没说有两只巨鳄
Well, she didn't want to tell us about the second croc,
她怕我们会把它轰死
'cause she was afraid we'd blow its head off.
她猜得真准
Women's intuition.
还有空位
We got room for one more.
最好有人跟来
Someone should probably go with him.
我得收拾东西
I'm still packing up some stuff,
但是
but, uh...
我去吧
I'll go.
你一定得写报告
So, I imagine you're gonna have a few reports to do.
有需要尽管找我
If you need anything, let me know.
很高兴认识你
Yeah. It was nice meeting you.
别这么情绪化嘛
Gee, Hank, don't get all choked up.
我拿你还是没辄
With you, I'm still mixed.
那就这样好了
Oh, well, then, just to offend you on principle, then.
再见
See you.
你想搭我的便车吗?
You want a ride in my truck?
前座放了东西
Oh, we just finished loading up the front of the truck.
要我拿走吗
Do you want us to take some stuff out?
不用了
No, no, that's all right.
我想再待一会儿
I'm gonna be a little while anyway.
向这座湖道别
I want to go say good-bye to the lake.
你确定? 我不介意
You sure, because I don't mind--
我真的想多待一会儿
No. I actually want to stay a little longer.
好吧
All right.
好
要是我去纽约
If I'm ever in New York, I'll...
是吗
Yeah.
缅因州男人都不会主动吗
So, does nobody ever make a move in Maine?
你只是把袋子移过去?
That's it? You slide your duffel bag?
上车吧 去喝杯啤酒
Just...get in the truck. Go for a beer.
镇上有家酒吧
There's a good bar in town.
一定很棒
Bet that's charming.
杯子干净吗
Are the glasses clean?
应该是吧
Mostly.
你要一直碎碎念吗?
You gonna complain the whole time?
杰克
Jack.
开车吧
Start the truck.
我已经开始想念那些鳄鱼了
I already miss the crocodile.
# I wanna love ya #
# And treat you right #
可爱的小鳄鱼
Cute little buttons. Oh, ho ho.
妈咪爱你们
Oh, mama loves you.
来吧
Come on.
吃晚饭了
Eat your supper.
咬咬妈咪的脚趾
Nibble mommy's toes.
很好
Yes.
# Roof right over our heads #
# We'll share the shelter #
# Of my single bed #
# We'll share the same room #
# Yeah #
# Jah provide the bread #
# Is this love, is this love #
# Is this love that I'm feeling? #
# That I'm feeling? #
# Oh, yes, I know, yes, I know #
# Yes, I know now #
# Am willing and able #
# Sol #
# Throw my cards on your table #
# See, I wanna love ya #
# I wanna love and treat ya #
# Love and treat ya right. #
# I wanna love ya #
# Every day and every night #
# We'll be together #
# With a roof right over our heads #
# We'll share the shelter #
# Of my single bed #
# We'll share the same room #
# Yeah #
# Jah provides the bread #
# We'll share the shelter #